(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026
#OmaruPolkaBirthdayFestival2026
新曲のお披露目あり！
New song reveal!
Glitter of Love
1/30 21:00~
ポルカのライブ過去最多 ホロメンゲスト 10名
Polka's live with the most Hololive guests ever: 10 guests!
遥か空
In the distant sky
響いてる
Echoing
祈りは
A prayer
奇跡に
Becomes a miracle
ETERNAL BLAZE
作詞：水樹奈々 作曲：上松範康 (Elements Garden)
Lyrics: Nana Mizuki / Comp: Noriyasu Agematsu (Elements Garden)
真赤な青に焦がれて
Yearning for the deep crimson blue
流れゆく涙の粒
Droplets of tears flow away
迷いなく包み込む
I encountered a warmth
温もりに出会った
That envelops me without hesitation
真っ白な雪のように
Words as honest as the pure white snow
どこまでも素直な言葉
Reaching everywhere
鉄の羽まとった
They start to move me
僕を動かしていく
Clad in wings of iron
傷つくたび 優しくなれる
Every time I get hurt, I can become kinder
君のその笑顔だけ
I want to protect only your smile
守り抜きたい 願いはひとつ
I have but one wish
時を越え刻まれた 悲しみの記憶
Memories of sadness carved across time
真っ直ぐに受け止める
I'll accept them head-on
君は光の戦士
You are a warrior of light
あの日胸に灯った
The eternal flame
永遠の炎
That was lit in my heart that day
深い闇解き放って
Unleashing the deep darkness
自由の扉開いてく
I'll open the door to freedom
強く果てない
Towards a strong and endless
未来へ
Future
冷たい緑の月に
A shadow of the heart projected
打ち出す心の影
Onto the cold green moon
寂しげに呟いた
I lonely whispered
君の側にいたい
"I want to be by your side"
真実と向き合うこと
The courage that taught me
教えてくれた勇気は
How to face the truth
僕を駆け巡って
Courses through me
夢に目覚めてゆく
And I awaken into a dream
触れ合う気持ち 離れないように
So that our touching feelings never separate
しっかりと抱きしめて
Hold me tight
確かな思い 貫いてゆく
I will see these certain feelings through
銀の海に隠した 空白のページ
A blank page hidden in a silver sea
君だけが知っている
Only you know
本当の僕を見せて
Show me the real me
吹き荒れる殺伐に
A vow born in the midst
生まれゆく誓い
Of a raging desolation
もう何も怖くないよ
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
結んだ視線そらさずに
Without looking away from our joined gaze
大切な今
I'll begin
始める
This precious "now"
君が君でいられる場所
So the place where you can be yourself
幻にさせぬように
Doesn't become an illusion
消えない雨の苦しみも
Even the pain of the unceasing rain
鍵を壊して
Break the lock
ぶつけてよ
Release it all
隣にいるから
For I am by your side
全てを信じて
Believe in everything
時を越え刻まれた 悲しみの記憶
Memories of sadness carved across time
真っ直ぐに受け止める
I'll accept them head-on
君は光の戦士
You are a warrior of light
あの日胸に灯った
The eternal flame
永遠の炎
That was lit in my heart that day
深い闇解き放って
Unleashing the deep darkness
自由の扉開いてく
I'll open the door to freedom
未来へー
To the future!
強く果てない未来へー
To a strong and endless future!
そう、いつどこから始まる
Yes, whenever and wherever it begins...
お待たせみんなー！
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
今年もポルカの誕生日が始まったー！
Polka's birthday celebration has begun again this year!
タイトルは、かっこいい、Glitter of Love！
The title is the cool-sounding "Glitter of Love"!
というわけで、
And so,
ハッシュタグはこちら！
here is the hashtag!
#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026で
Please use #OmaruPolkaBirthday2026 and
いっぱい、いっぱい、呟いてね！はい！
tweet about it lots and lots! Okay!
いやー、今回のテーマがまず、愛と勇気と戦う女の子になってます。
Well, first off, the theme this time is "a girl who fights with love and courage."
そして、
And also,
見てください、このステージ！えい！
look at this stage! Tah-dah!
はぁー、すごい広い。おー。
Wow, it's so huge. Ohhh.
なんとですね、広いんですけど、まずスクリーンが超大きい！
Can you believe how big it is? And the screen is giant!
大迫力！
What an impact!
なんと、なんかいつもの3倍くらい頑張りました。
I worked about three times as hard as usual on this.
いや、頑張ってもらいました。
Or rather, I had everyone work that hard for me.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
というわけでですね、ここからゲストの方々が、たくさんいらっしゃいます。
And now, we have a lot of guests coming on.
もうホロメンだけなら、多分尾丸ポルカ史上最多のゲスト数だと思っております。
Counting just Hololive members, I think it's the most guests I've ever had.
それをね、これからノンストップでお送りするので、楽しんでいってください！
We'll be presenting them non-stop from here, so please enjoy!
というわけで、行くぞー！
Alright then, let's go!
遺伝子レベルの
On a genetic level...
Independence
絶望も希望も
Despair and hope alike,
抱いて
embrace them.
あがけ命尽きるまで
Struggle until your life is spent.
星天ギャラクシィクロス
作詞・作曲：上松範康(Elements Garden)
Seiten Galaxy Cross
Lyrics/Composition: Noriyasu Agematsu (Elements Garden)
光と飛沫のKiss 恋のような虹のバースデイ
A kiss of light and spray, a rainbow birthday like love.
どんな美しき日も 何か生まれ 何かが死ぬ
No matter how beautiful the day, something is born and something dies.
せめて歌おう I love you 世界が地獄だとしても
At least let's sing "I love you," even if the world is hell.
せめて伝えよう I love you 解放の時は来た
At least let's convey "I love you," the time for liberation has come.
星降る天へと 響き飛べ Every body song
To the starry heavens, echo and fly, everybody's song!
Stardust
そして奇跡は 待つものじゃなくて
And miracles aren't something to wait for,
その手で創るものと 吠えろ
they are things you create with those hands. Roar!
涙した過去への鎮魂歌をレクイエムにして
Turn the requiem for a tearful past into a song.
聖なる全力 全智 全力で
With sacred all-out power, all-out wisdom and power!
輝けFuture 信じ照らせ 星天ギャラクシィクロス
Shine, Future! Believe and illuminate, Seiten Galaxy Cross!
一人じゃないことを やがて君は知る日のため
For the day you finally realize you are not alone,
指先伝うアストロ 分かち合って明日へ向かう
astro traveling through fingertips, let's share and head for tomorrow.
永遠なる空に I feel you 自由の魂は 閉ざせはしない
In the eternal sky, I feel you. The soul of freedom will not be closed off!
不滅なる夢に I feel you 未来へと手を握れ
In an immortal dream, I feel you. Grasp hands toward the future!
運命も 終極も 断ち切る力で
With the power to cut through fate and the ultimate end!
そして重ねた夢を
And these overlapping dreams...
ドキドキ 煌めき
My heart's pounding, a sparkling glow,
十字となって闇を暴く
Forming a cross to expose the darkness.
駆け抜けたその丘には
On that hill we ran through,
神様も知らない
Even the gods don't know...
歴史が光
...the light of history.
踊る My top and Brave Heart
Dancing with my top and brave heart,
この大きな奇跡(きずな) 星天ギャラクシィクロス
This great miracle—this bond—Seiten Galaxy Cross.
Trio Dreams
作詞：大森祥子 作曲：佐藤あき子
Lyrics: Sachiko Omori / Composition: Akiko Sato
Let's sing! Let's swing! Let's dance! Let's burn!
Let's smile! Let's fly! Woo! PreCure!!!
ときめきで上書きした世界 未来
A world and future overwritten with excitement,
1+1+1は無限
1+1+1 is infinity!
唇からこぼれる歌は ラ・ラ・リラ・ラ
A song spilling from our lips, la-la-lila-la,
リズム眩しい光 ラ・ラ・シャ・サンシャイン
A dazzling light of rhythm, la-la-sha-sunshine.
三人寄れば文殊最高 最強
Three heads are better than one—the best, the strongest!
始まるただ一度のラフ＆エンジョイ トゥゲザー
Starting our one-and-only Rough & Enjoy together.
ハミング ジャスト オフ 完奏ね 交差レスポンス
Humming, Just of, the performance is complete, a crossing response,
輝きプリデイいいよね
A sparkling pre-day is great, isn't it?
好きな 好きな フレーズを
Taking our favorite, favorite phrases,
シンフォニーに夢をのせて
Putting our dreams on a symphony,
君 あなたの元へ For you
to you, to where you are, for you.
もっともっと輝き合えるね
We can shine together even more,
みんな (Yeah! Yeah!)
everyone! (Yeah! Yeah!)
瞳スクリーンにいつだって
On the screen of our eyes, let's always
笑顔映し合おう
reflect each other's smiles.
Promise 君がいるからパワー生まれるよ 今日も
Promise, because you're here, power is born, today too!
Let's sing! Let's swing! Let's dance! Let's burn!
Let's smile! Let's fly! Woo! PreCure!!!
一緒だから感じるハッピー ワンピ
Because we're together, we feel happy, one-piece,
1×1×1は無敵
1×1×1 is invincible!
出し惜しみはなしで全部あげたい ラ・ラ・リラ・ラ
Without holding anything back, I want to give it all, la-la-lila-la.
ハプニングさえチョイス ワン・トゥー
Even choosing the happenings, one-two,
三人寄れば文殊もしの 知能
Three heads together, a charging wisdom,
見せるよきっと伝説のライブ アンコールちょっと
We'll surely show you a legendary live, with a little encore.
Jump & Hop Step Sun-Sun All welcome
カテゴリライズいらないね
No need for categorization,
好きだ 好きだ 思いきり
I love it, I love it, with all my heart!
Shout & Flow 羽ひろげ
Shout & Flow, spread your wings
はばたこう その奥へ For you
and fly deeper, for you.
命は輝きでできて
Life is made of brilliance,
いるの (Yeah! Yeah!)
you know? (Yeah! Yeah!)
ビッグスクリーンもはみ出しちゃう
Spilling out of the big screen,
嬉しいや楽しい
happiness and fun.
Plus 君を知って 知らない自分に会えたよ
Plus, knowing you, I met a version of myself I never knew.
Let's sing! Let's swing! Let's dance! Let's burn!
Let's smile! Let's fly!
PreCure!!!
Let's sing! Let's swing! Let's dance! Let's burn!
Let's smile! Let's fly!
輝きプリデイいいよね
A sparkling pre-day is great, isn't it?
好きな 好きな フレーズを
Taking our favorite, favorite phrases,
シンフォニーに夢をのせて
Putting our dreams on a symphony,
君 あなたの元へ For you
to you, to where you are, for you.
もっともっと輝き合えるね
We can shine together even more,
みんな (Yeah! Yeah!)
everyone! (Yeah! Yeah!)
瞳スクリーンにいつだって
On the screen of our eyes, let's always
笑顔...
reflect smiles...
もっと美しい方へ
Towards a more beautiful place
君がいるからパワー 生まれるよ今日も
Because you are here, power is born today too
Let's try Trio Dreams
Let's sing Let's swing Let's dance Let's ball Let's smile Let's fight Woo Please go
Let's sing Let's swing Let's dance Let's ball Let's smile Let's fight
Awakening Harmony
暗闇の真ん中
In the middle of darkness
真っ直ぐな眼差し
A straight gaze
立ち上がる姿 ちゃんと見ていたよ
I was watching your figure as you stood up
閉じ込められそうな 心を奮い立たせ
Stirring up the heart that seemed likely to be trapped
収まりきらない 輝きを放ち
Releasing a brilliance that cannot be contained
射抜かれた胸の奥
Deep in the heart that was shot through
焼き付いたままの熱さは
The heat that remains scorched in
それだけでも 自由になれるって言って
Say that even that alone can set me free
取り戻したい 光の世界
The world of light I want to take back
その笑顔 勇気 涙 夢 希望の陽射し
That smile, courage, tears, dreams, rays of hope
君と明日を 願う力で生まれる
Born from the power of wishing for tomorrow with you
私たちのハーモニー 響け
Let our harmony resound
それでも暗闇は 訪れてしまうもの
Even so, darkness is something that visits
惑わされないで 君は君だから
Don't be led astray, because you are you
分かち合えた日々が 心を輝かせる
The days we shared make the heart shine
一人じゃないこと 気付かせてくれる
Letting me realize I'm not alone
抱えきれないほどの ありがとうの代わりに
Instead of more thank-yous than I can carry
鍵をかけて 一つになる 受け止めて
Lock it up, become one, accept it
取り戻すんだ 光の未来
I'll take back the future of light
今 熱い思い つないで 叶えに行くよ
Connecting hot feelings now, I'm going to make them come true
君と一緒に 願える奇跡
A miracle we can wish for together
重ねて 広がっていくハーモニー 響け
Layering, the expanding harmony, resound
目覚める時が来たね
The time to wake up has come
本当の自分になる
Becoming my true self
導く運命
A destiny that guides
取り戻したい 光の世界
The world of light I want to take back
その笑顔 勇気 涙 夢 希望の陽射し
That smile, courage, tears, dreams, rays of hope
君と明日を 願う力で生まれる
Born from the power of wishing for tomorrow with you
私たちのハーモニー 響け
Let our harmony resound
トライアングル・ドリーマー
Triangle Dreamer
Day by day 日に日に 募る乙女心
Day by day, day by day, growing maiden's heart
同じ
Same
いつだって クラスで ななめ前の おとなしい人
In our class, it's always the quiet person sitting diagonally in front of me.
さあ かっこよくはない だけど優しい
Well, he's not exactly cool, but he's kind.
いつも 頼れる 彼
He's someone I can always count on.
放課後 恋愛 相談の 帰り道
On the way home after school, talking about love.
なんだって 話せる 親友の 女の子
The girl who's my best friend, I can talk to her about anything.
スポーツ万能で 勉強もできて
She's great at sports and good at studying, too.
女子力 マックスです
Her feminine charm is at its max.
どこにでもある よくあること
It's a common story you'd find anywhere.
急に 彼女が
Suddenly, she says...
「あのね 実は 私 好きな人が いるの」って
"You know, the truth is, I have someone I like."
ちょっマジで!?
Wait, for real!?
三角 三角の恋は 気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle of love is so fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬で 崩れる バランス
In an instant, the balance crumbles in an instant.
ベタな 漫画 みたいな フラグ
A cliche flag just like in a manga.
まさか 自分を 立てちゃうなんて 残念すぎます
I can't believe I'm the one who set it off; it's so regrettable.
三角 三角の恋は 不安定
Triangle, a triangle of love is unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ 済まない カテゴリー
It's not a category you can just say "just kidding" to.
恋と 友情 ゆらゆら 揺れて
Swaying between love and friendship.
なんか 青春 しちゃいます
It feels like I'm experiencing youth.
私 困っちゃいます
I'm at a loss.
乾杯で お似合いすぎるわ さて困った
They look so good together as they toast, what should I do?
悔しいけど どこか そんなんじゃなくて 本心
It's frustrating, but it's not like that; it's my true feelings.
っていうか 既に 応援 モード
Actually, I'm already in cheering mode.
むしろ 清々しい
It's actually quite refreshing.
だけど 彼女は 不思議な顔
But she has a strange look on her face.
真剣な目で
With serious eyes...
「そうじゃなくて 私 あなたが好き ごめん」って
"No, that's not it. I like you. I'm sorry."
ちょっマジで!?
Wait, for real!?
三角 三角の恋は 気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle of love is so fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬で 崩れる バランス
In an instant, the balance crumbles in an instant.
私 あなた 彼女と 私
Me and you, her and me.
超絶 複雑 有利展開は 想定外です
It's super complex, this favorable development was unexpected.
三角 三角の恋は 不安定
Triangle, a triangle of love is unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ 済まない カテゴリー
It's not a category you can just say "just kidding" to.
解けない パズル 与えたもうた
A puzzle that cannot be solved was given to me.
神よ 恨んじゃいます
Oh God, I'm starting to resent you.
私 悩んじゃいます
I'm worrying over this.
あー もう すごい ヤバイ 聞いてる?
Ah, geez, this is crazy! Are you listening?
聞いたけど
I heard you, but...
えっ そういう意味じゃなくて だって 女の子同士だし
Eh, that's not what I mean. But we're both girls!
ねえ 神様 どうしたらいいの?
Hey God, what should I do?
私 どうしたいの? HELP ME!
What do I want to do? Help me!
なんか 変だ 愛に 国境も 年も 性別も 関係ない
Something's strange. Love knows no borders, age, or gender.
けど けど けど...
But, but, but...
三角 三角の恋は 気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle of love is so fickle.
一瞬で 一瞬で 崩れる バランス
In an instant, the balance crumbles in an instant.
普通の 恋 夢見てたのに
Even though I dreamed of a normal love...
ノーマル 捨てての 私じゃ ちょっと 無理ゲーすぎます
Throwing away "normal," this is a bit too much of a "no-win game."
三角 三角の恋は 不安定
Triangle, a triangle of love is unstable.
なんちゃって なんちゃってじゃ 済まない カテゴリー
It's not a category you can just say "just kidding" to.
彼女の こと 好きに なれたら
If only I could fall in love with her...
なんて 妄想 しちゃいます
I find myself daydreaming about that.
私 どかしちゃってます
I'm going a bit crazy.
煌々と続くショート・ショート
Glittering and continuing short short
奏した絶対零度
Playing with absolute zero
今夜輪廻衝 悲しみが
Tonight in the cycle of rebirth, sadness...
混沌の木漏れ日歌ってるよ
Is singing in the chaotic sunlight filtering through trees
運命に理由があるのならば
If there is a reason for destiny
全てを懸けてみたいの
I want to try staking everything
あなたを守りたい
I want to protect you
何処までも高く飛べるわ
I can fly higher than anywhere
何処までも強く 強くなれるわ
I can become stronger and stronger, anywhere
信じて 私に出会えた奇跡
Believe in the miracle of meeting me
切り拓く不死鳥の炎抱いて
Paving the way, embracing the flames of the phoenix
あなたの傍では
By your side
高鳴る眼差し抱きたくなるの
I want to hold your throbbing gaze
Flashback Flashback 振り解け
Flashback Flashback, shake it off
焦燥 挑み続けろ
Keep challenging the impatience
飄々と佇むホット・ショット
A hot shot standing coolly
私が必要でしょう
You'll need me, right?
今夜輪廻衝 正しさが
Tonight in the cycle of rebirth, correctness...
逸脱 最前線に押し出すよ
Is pushing out to the forefront of deviation
運命に理由があるのならば
If there is a reason for destiny
優しい世界をあげたい
I want to give you a gentle world
あなたを包むわ
I will wrap around you
何処までも速く射抜くわ
I will shoot through as fast as anywhere
何処までも熱く 熱く焦がすわ
I will burn hotly, hotly, anywhere
信じて 私に出会えた奇跡
Believe in the miracle of meeting me
切り拓く不死鳥の炎抱いて
Paving the way, embracing the flames of the phoenix
あなたの傍では 正しい光を見せて
By your side, show me the true light
Flashback Flashback 許さない
Flashback Flashback, I won't allow it
Goodbye 進み続けろ
Goodbye, keep moving forward
尽きるまで
Until it burns out
傍に居ると
When I'm by your side
鼓動が速くて目眩がする
My heartbeat is so fast, it makes me dizzy
全て捧げる もう決めたの
I've already decided to give everything
最後のチャンスだから もう離さない
It's the last chance, so I won't let go anymore
あなたに舞い降りる 未来の風
The wind of the future alighting on you
跨って行け
Ride it and go
何処までも高く飛べるわ
I can fly higher than anywhere
何処までも強く 強くなれるわ
I can become stronger and stronger, anywhere
信じて 私に出会えた奇跡
Believe in the miracle of meeting me
闇夜も望めば輝かすから
Because even the dark night will shine if you wish it
切り拓く不死鳥の炎抱いて
Paving the way, embracing the flames of the phoenix
あなたの傍では 高鳴る眼差し抱きたくなるの
By your side, I want to hold your throbbing gaze
Flashback Flashback 振り解け
Flashback Flashback, shake it off
焦燥 挑み続けろ
Keep challenging the impatience
高鳴る眼差し抱きたくなるの
I want to hold your throbbing gaze
Flashback Flashback 許さない
Flashback Flashback, I won't allow it
Goodbye 進み続けろ
Goodbye, keep moving forward
Woh woh woh...
ダイアモンド クレバス
Diamond Crevasse
神様に恋をしていた頃は
Back when I was in love with God...
こんな別れが来るとは思ってなかったよ
I never thought such a parting would come.
Uh...
もう二度と触れられないなら
If I can never touch you again...
せめて最後に
then at least one last time...
もう一度抱きしめて欲しかったよ
I wanted you to hold me once more.
Uh... It's long long goodbye
サヨナラ サヨナラ 何度だって
Goodbye, goodbye, no matter how many times...
自分に 無情に言い聞かせて
I heartlessly tell myself.
手を振るのは優しさだよね
Waving goodbye is a kind of kindness, right?
今 強さが欲しい
I want strength right now.
あなたに出会い 輝いてあたしが生まれて
Meeting you, I shone, and I was born.
愛すればこそ
Precisely because I love you...
愛あればこそ
precisely because there is love...
希望のない奇跡を待ってどうなるの
what happens if I wait for a miracle without hope?
涙ににじむ 星の瞬きは go...
The twinkling of stars, blurred by tears, go...
(Vocalizing)
忘れないよ
I won't forget...
あなたのぬくもりも その優しさも
your warmth and that kindness...
全て包んでくれた両手も
or the hands that wrapped everything up.
Uh... It's long long goodbye
サヨナラ サヨナラ 愛おしい人
Goodbye, goodbye, my beloved.
あなたがいたから 歩いてこれた
Because you were there, I was able to walk on.
一人なんかじゃなかったよね
I wasn't alone, was I?
今 答えが欲しい
I want an answer right now.
燃えるような流星捕まえて
Catching a burning shooting star...
火を灯して
and lighting a fire...
愛していたい
I want to keep loving you...
愛されてたい
I want to keep being loved.
切れた体一つで世界はどうなるの
With just a torn body, what will happen to the world?
張りつめ続けてた
My bluff...
虚勢が溶けて long fall
that I've kept strained melts away, long fall.
どうしてなの 涙あふれて
Why is it? Tears overflow...
止められない
and I can't stop them.
あなたに出会い 輝いてあたしが生まれて
Meeting you, I shone, and I was born.
愛すればこそ
Precisely because I love you...
愛あればこそ
precisely because there is love...
希望のない奇跡を待ってどうなるの
what happens if I wait for a miracle without hope?
涙ににじむ 星の瞬きは go...
The twinkling of stars, blurred by tears, go...
もし生まれ変わって また巡り会えるのなら
If I am reborn and we can meet again...
その時もきっと あたしを見つけだして
then surely find me even then.
もう二度と離さないで捕まえてて
Catch me and never let go again.
一人じゃないとささやいて
Whisper that I'm not alone.
...て欲しい プラネット
...I want you to be... Planet
Paradise Lost
作詞：畑 亜貴 作曲：菊田 大介
Lyrics: Aki Hata, Composition: Daisuke Kikuta
聖なる瞳が
The sacred eyes
痛みを映したら
If they reflect pain
振り向いてご覧
Turn around and see
情熱放つトリック
A trick that releases passion
崩れる足元
The ground is crumbling
二人は戻れない
The two of us can't go back
差し延べた手を解かないで
Don't let go of the outstretched hand
消えるよまた
They disappear again
優しい日々が
The gentle days
思い出を汚すのは 許せない
I can't forgive staining the memories
ここは裏切りのティナ・ノーレ
This is the Tina Nore of betrayal
彷徨う心の果てに
At the end of a wandering heart
光を求めて
Seeking the light
祈る言葉届けあなたに
May my prayer reach you
囚われの羽が
The captive wings
遥かな空へと向かう
Head towards the distant sky
信じたいよ私たち
I want to believe, we are...
孤独じゃない
...not alone
分かり合える
We can understand each other
求め合える
We can seek each other
絆の中で
Within our bonds
離さない
I won't let go
離れない
I won't leave
始まるディスティニー
The destiny begins
新たな願いに
In a new wish
鎖解ける時
When the chains are undone
安らわせてくれる
Giving me peace
深い眠りに
In a deep sleep
僅かな希望が
A tiny hope
私を強くする
Makes me stronger
ぬくもりに触れてみたいから
Because I want to feel the warmth
蘇れば
If it is resurrected
儚き命
The fleeting life
繰り返す愛しさが導いた
Led by the recurring affection
胸に打つ鼓動の調べ
The melody of the beating heart
流れる世界の終わり
The end of the flowing world
諦めはしない
I won't give up
今が繋ぐ明日探そう
Let's find the tomorrow connected to now
千切れ舞う羽は
The torn, dancing wings
未来の空にも向かう
Also head towards the future sky
忘れないで私たち
Don't forget, we are...
一つのクリスタル
...one crystal
輝いて
Shining
羽ばたいて
Flapping wings
割れないのよ
It won't break
離さない
I won't let go
離れない
I won't leave
誓いのディスティニー
The destiny of the vow
消えるよまた
They disappear again
優しい日々が
The gentle days
思い出を汚すのは 許せない
I can't forgive staining the memories
ここは裏切りのティナ・ノーレ
This is the Tina Nore of betrayal
彷徨う心の果てに
At the end of a wandering heart
光を求めて
Seeking the light
祈る言葉届けあなたに
May my prayer reach you
囚われの羽が
The captive wings
遥かな空へと向かう
Head towards the distant sky
信じたいよ私たち
I want to believe, we are...
孤独じゃない
...not alone
分かり合える
We can understand each other
求め合える
We can seek each other
絆の中で
Within our bonds
離さない...
I won't let go...
見つめて Paradise Lost
Look at me, Paradise Lost
Whoa whoa whoa...
やっとみんな会えたね
Finally, we can all meet.
Das ist unsre Definitive!
This is our definitive!
GIRLS' LEGEND U
Das ist unsre Definitive!
This is our definitive!
掲げた全力 走りたい
With all my might, I want to run
芝と 砂と 君の追い切りメニュー
Turf and dirt, and your final training menu
ランナー、ランナー 声出して叫べ
Runner, runner! Raise your voice and shout
Whoa...
とりあえず ファイ！ オー！ ファイ！ オー！
For now, fight! oh! fight! oh!
掲げた全力 上がりたい
With all my might, I want to rise up
譲れない夢の途中
In the middle of an unyielding dream
Whoa...
始めよう ここから最高ストーリー
Let's start the greatest story from here
Oh oh oh oh...
あぁ 憧れの地へ
Ah, to the land of my dreams
少し 痛い
A little painful
語り合ったメモリー
The memories we shared
一歩進むたびに
With every step I take
もっと ドキドキ もっと トキメキ
More heartbeat, more excitement
抑えられない たまんない
I can't hold it back, it's unbearable
熱いハラハラが止まらない
The burning suspense won't stop
君と 走り競い ゴール目指し
Racing with you, aiming for the goal
遥か響け 届けミュージック
Ring out into the distance, reach out music
ずっと ずっと ずっと 想い
Forever, forever, forever, my feelings...
夢はきっと叶うから
Because dreams will surely come true
あの日君に感じた
What I felt from you that day,
何かを信じて
believing in something...
春も夏も秋も冬も 声願い焦がれ走れ
Spring, summer, autumn, winter, my voice, my wish, longing, run
あぁ 勝利へ
Ah, toward victory
Das ist unsre Definitive!
This is our definitive!
掲げた全力 弾けたい
With all my might, I want to burst out
大出会い 決意 絆になった
A great encounter, determination, it became a bond
ハンズアップ！ ハンズアップ！ 本気で叫べ
Hands up! Hands up! Shout with all your heart
Whoa...
とりあえず ファイ！ オー！ ファイ！ オー！
For now, fight! oh! fight! oh!
掲げた全力 笑いたい
With all my might, I want to laugh
ゴールど真ん中
Right in the middle of the goal
Whoa...
リアルに ここから上昇ストーリー
Realistically, a rising story from here
Oh oh oh oh...
駆け抜けた日々
The days we raced through
少し 苦い
A little bitter
語り合ったグローリー
The glory we shared
強くなるたびに
Every time I get stronger
今 応えたい 生きてると
Now I want to answer, that I'm alive
背中を少し 熱く鳴る
My back feels a bit warm
夢は夢のまま終われない
Dreams cannot end just as dreams
君と 未来描き ゴール目指し
Painting the future with you, aiming for the goal
狙い挑め 掴めウィニング
Aim, challenge, seize the winning
ずっと ずっと ずっと 想い
Forever, forever, forever, my feelings...
夢はきっと叶うから
Because dreams will surely come true
あの日君が鳴らした
What you sounded that day,
涙も信じて
believing even in tears...
雨も風も雲も闇も 声願い焦がれ走れ
Rain, wind, clouds, darkness, my voice, my wish, longing, run
あぁ 勝利へ
Ah, toward victory
揺るぎない覚悟決して
With unyielding determination,
一つ二つ共に綴る記録
one and two, records we write together
背中に迫る迷い振り払え
Shake off the hesitation closing in behind you
今の自分追い越すだけ
Just overtake your current self
勝ちたい 勝ちたい 勝ちたい
I want to win, want to win, want to win
君と勝ちたい
I want to win with you
未来描き ゴール目指し
Painting the future, aiming for the goal
狙い挑め 掴めウィニング
Aim, challenge, seize the winning
ずっと ずっと ずっと 想い
Forever, forever, forever, my feelings...
夢はきっと叶うから
Because dreams will surely come true
あの日君が鳴らした
What you sounded that day,
涙も信じて
believing even in tears...
春も夏も秋も冬も 声雨も風も超え
Spring, summer, autumn, winter, voice, transcending rain and wind...
雲も闇も超え 勝利へ
transcending clouds and darkness, toward victory
走り競い ゴール目指し
Racing, aiming for the goal
遥か響け 届けミュージック
Ring out into the distance, reach out music
ずっと ずっと ずっと 想い
Forever, forever, forever, my feelings...
夢はきっと叶うから
Because dreams will surely come true
あの日君に感じた
What I felt from you that day,
何かを信じて
believing in something...
春も夏も秋も冬も 声願い焦がれ走れ
Spring, summer, autumn, winter, my voice, my wish, longing, run
あぁ 勝利へ
Ah, toward victory
未来描きゴール目指し 狙い定め掴め Winning
Charting the future, aiming for the goal; steady your aim and seize the victory
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い
Always, always, always, always dreaming
夢はきっと叶うから
Dreams will surely come true
あの日君が流した
The tears you shed that day
涙も信じて
Believe in them too
雨も風も雲も闇も超え
Beyond the rain, wind, clouds, and darkness
願い焦がれ走れ
Run with a yearning heart
ああ 勝利へ
Ah, towards victory
Don't stop, non stop to the finish.
Don't stop, non-stop to the finish.
STARTING OVER
作詞：乙女ましろ 作曲・編曲：朝日 圭太
Lyrics: Otome Mashiro / Composition & Arrangement: Keita Asahi
It's finally the true end.
I'm ready for... my destiny.
I'm ready for... STARTING OVER.
やっと幕を下ろせた
Finally, the curtain has fallen
最後の瞬間まで
Until the very last moment
わたしは精一杯に
With all my heart and soul
わたしをやりきった
I gave it my all
終演の続きは
What comes after the performance
誰も知らなくていい
Doesn't need to be known by anyone
涙を置いて
Leaving the tears behind
新しい旅に出よう
Let's set out on a new journey
熱狂はあなたを選ぶ
The frenzy chooses you
違う結末だっただけ
It was just a different ending
同じ愛になれなかった
We couldn't become the same love
Destiny
これまでの全てを
Everything up until now
差し出すような愛だった
Was a love like offering my all
世界の意味が変わるくらいに
So much that the meaning of the world changed
肯定された気がしたんだ
I felt like I was affirmed
何気なさの中で
In the midst of the ordinary
気づけた最初の奇跡が
The first miracle I noticed
あなたでよかった わたしでよかった
I'm glad it was you, I'm glad it was me
心から思えたよ
I could truly feel it from my heart
ずっと遠い未来も
Even in the far-off future
ちゃんと覚えていよう
Let's remember it well
自分の抱きしめかた
How to embrace myself
明日の願いかた
How to pray for tomorrow
あなたがいなくても
Even if you're not here
わたしの片隅で
In a corner of my heart
優しい光
A gentle light
消えたりしないとわかる
I know it won't ever fade
今はまだ手を振れるほど
Still just barely enough to wave
道は別れたばかりで
The paths have only just diverged
後ろ髪に風を
Feeling the wind in my hair
感じながら
As I look back
それまでの全てが
Everything up until then
あなたに出会うためだった
Was for the sake of meeting you
どの瞬間もムダじゃないこと
That not a single moment was wasted
本当の意味で知れたから
Because I've learned its true meaning
次の曲がり角も
Even at the next turn
自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose as myself
いつかに繋がる 新しい一歩
A new step leading to some day
信じて歩き出そう
Let's start walking with belief
心から誰かを愛せた
Being able to love someone from my heart
あの日々は
Those days
間違いなくわたしの
Are unmistakably my
Destiny Ah
これまでの全てが 新しい力をくれる
Everything up until now gives me new strength
どの瞬間もムダじゃないなら
If not a single moment is wasted
何が起きても大丈夫だから
Then whatever happens, it'll be okay
次の物語も
The next story, too
自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose as myself
いつかに繋がる わたしのはじまり
My beginning leading to some day
信じて歩き出そう
Let's start walking with belief
いつかに繋がる　わたしのはじまり　信じて歩き出そう
Someday it will lead somewhere, my beginning. Let's start walking with faith.
再び幕は上がる
The curtain rises again.
聴いていただいたのは新曲の『STARTING OVER』でした！
That was my new song, "STARTING OVER"!
はい、新年一発目、新曲の初披露というわけで
Yes, it's the first new song reveal of the year.
ぬるっとね、新曲をやってしまったんですが
I just sort of smoothly played the new song...
平成感のある、え、懐かしみの感じの楽曲を
A song with a Heisei-era feel, you know, with a nostalgic touch.
こちらですね、歌わせていただいたんですけども
That's what I sang for you today.
この後、この曲が、え、24時から、あと数時間か、
After this, at midnight tonight—only a few hours away—
1月30日の24時から配信リリースされます！
it will be released on streaming platforms from midnight on January 30th!
たくさん聴いてください！
Please listen to it a lot!
今年もね、たくさんオリ曲出していきたいです！
I want to release many original songs this year too!
そしてそして、もうMCがね、実は最後なのでね、
And also, this is actually the last MC segment...
この配信の後にはメンバー限定の配信もあるので、よろしくお願いします！
After this stream, there'll be a members-only stream, so please join us there!
よしよしよし、グッズ紹介！
All right, all right, all right! Merchandise reveal!
えー、ここには同期のねぽらぼが大集合ということで、
And we have the whole NePoLaBo crew here together...
ね、ら、ぼ、集まれー！
Ne, Ra, Bo, come on out!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい、ちゃちゃちゃ、初めて呼びました。どうも。
Yes, cha-cha-cha, first time I called you like that. Hello.
あれ、初だっけ？ ポルカチャンネル初です。
Wait, is this the first time? It's the first time on Polka's channel.
ポルカチャンネルの皆様、お誕生日おめでとう！おめでとう！ありがとう！
Everyone on the Polka Channel, Happy Birthday! Congratulations! Thank you!
ここまでが流れでございます。はい。
That's how the flow goes. Yes.
ずっと待ってたから。待ってたよ。
We've been waiting forever. We were waiting.
グッズを紹介させていただきたいと思います。
I'd like to introduce the merchandise.
乱入しながらのリアクションなど、各々取って頂けると嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you guys could give your reactions while barging in.
ガヤ担当！ガヤガヤ。
We're in charge of the noise! Noise, noise...
というわけで、尾丸ポルカ誕生日記念グッズ2026、ラインナップはこちら！
So, here's the lineup for the Omaru Polka Birthday Celebration Goods 2026!
ドーン！ドーン！
Boom! Boom!
というわけで、素晴らしい今回もラインナップが揃っております！
So, we have a wonderful lineup again this time!
おー！すごーい！あれ？ちょっと...あれれ？エチエチじゃない？
Oh! Amazing! Wait, a little... Huh? Isn't that a bit lewd?
ポルカさん、ちょっと、なんか盛ってます？盛ってませんよ！盛ってません！
Polka-san, are you, like, padding a bit? I'm not padding! I'm not!
というわけで、まず一つ一つ紹介していきましょう！
Anyway, let's introduce them one by one!
まずは、こちら！はい！
First up, this one! Yes!
ポルカのはじめての抱き枕カバーになっております！
It's Polka's first-ever body pillow cover!
すごーい！かわいい！
Amazing! So cute!
え、ちょっとポルカさん、ちょっとパンツ履いてません？あれ？生足じゃないですか？
Wait, Polka-san, are you not wearing underwear? Wait, aren't those bare legs?
いや、履いてます！履いてます！え、そんな部屋着だよ。
No, I'm wearing them! I am! Hey, that's just loungewear.
部屋着だよ。だって、ねねとかなってこういう部屋着だもん。まあ...まあまあまあ。
It's loungewear. I mean, Nene and the others wear loungewear like this. Well... well, well, well.
わちゃわちゃわちゃ。ステイステイステイ！人のチャンネルだからってやりたい放題チャンネルして！
Noisy chatter. Stay, stay, stay! Just because it's someone else's channel doesn't mean you can do whatever you want!
お前、シャツで寝たらシワつくぞ。
You'll get wrinkles if you sleep in a shirt like that.
おい、マジレス！写真撮影用かもしれないですよ。
Hey, don't be so realistic! It might just be for the photo shoot.
なるほどね。
I see.
というわけで、初めて抱き枕カバー出します。
So, I'm releasing a body pillow cover for the first time.
表が通常衣装で、裏は彼シャツになってます！
The front is the usual outfit, and the back is the "boyfriend's shirt" look!
おー！彼シャツ！彼シャツいただきました！
Oh! Boyfriend's shirt! We got the boyfriend's shirt look!
はい、ありがとうね。パセリ先生、ありがとう！
Yes, thank you. Parsley-sensei, thank you!
続きまして、ドン！こちら！
Moving on, boom! This one!
歴代衣装のポルカ、ランダムラバーストラップです！
It's the random rubber straps of Polka's past outfits!
おー！かわいい！
Oh! So cute!
これまでの衣装のラバーストラップ、こちら、のいみぬ先生に描いていただきました！
The rubber straps of my previous outfits, these were drawn by Noiminu-sensei!
え、めっちゃいいじゃん、これ。かわいいー。
Hey, this is really nice. So cute.
どの衣装が出るかお楽しみに！ありがとうね、みんなリアクション。本当に100点満点です。
Look forward to seeing which outfit you get! Thank you everyone for the reactions. Truly a perfect score.
はい、続きまして、こちら！
Yes, moving on, this one!
『どれもこれも宝物』思い出バインダー！
The "Everything is a Treasure" Memory Binder!
おー、いいね！かわいい！
Oh, nice! So cute!
これですね、最近みんなも特典でチェキ風ブロマイドカード出したりしてるから、そういうの入れられたり、
This is because lately everyone's been releasing cheki-style bromide cards as bonuses, so you can put those in here,
あとはホロカも入るサイズになっていますので、ぜひぜひ色んな思い出しまってください！しまってください！
and it's also the right size for Hololive cards, so please, store all kinds of memories in it! Please store them!
はい、そして続きましては、こちら！
Yes, and moving on, this one!
ポルカのしっぽキーホルダー！
Polka's Tail Keychain!
おー！かわいい！一周して流行ってるからね！
Oh! So cute! It's back in style now!
ポルカのしっぽ型のキーホルダー。
A keychain in the shape of Polka's tail.
確かに確かに。
True, true.
平成レトロ、みたいな感じで。
Like a Heisei retro vibe.
平成レトロみたいな感じで出ております。はい、こちらを付けてください！
It's out with a Heisei retro kind of feel. Yes, please put this on!
そしてボイスも出ます！ボイスはこちら！じゃん！
And there's a voice pack too! Here it is! Ta-da!
何？ASMRボイスです！
What? It's an ASMR voice pack!
おー！はい、えーと、ま、彼シャツのポルカ、という...
Oh! Yes, well, the "boyfriend's shirt" Polka...
ちょっとタイトルもなんか...
The title is also kind of...
狙ってるじゃん！エチエチフルコンボ！やめてよ！
You're totally aiming for it! Lewd full combo! Stop it!
フルコンボだドン！なんで今日同期呼んじゃったんだろうっていうのを一瞬思った今。恥ずかしくなってきた。
Full combo! "Why did I invite my gen-mates today?" is what I'm thinking for a second just now. I'm starting to get embarrassed.
ガチ照れ！
She's legitimately blushing!
え、え、え、えっと...添い寝ASMRというか、抱き枕カバーとイラストの関係がある内容になってます！お楽しみに！
U-u-u-uh... it's like a co-sleeping ASMR, and it's related to the body pillow cover illustration. Look forward to it!
おー！
Oh!
はい、皆様お待たせしました。フルセット購入特典になっております。こちら！
Yes, thanks for waiting, everyone. Here's the full set purchase bonus! This one!
チェキ風ブロマイドカード、数量限定が直筆メッセージ、箔押し複製サインになっております！
The cheki-style bromide card. The limited quantity version has a handwritten message and a foil-stamped replica signature!
おー！いい！
Oh! Nice!
通常が箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入りでございます。
The regular version has a foil-stamped replica signature and a message.
フルセットぜひぜひ買っていただいた方には！
And for those who buy the full set!
特典ボイスとして、すやすやポルカのね、添い寝ボイスというか... エチエチエチエチエチ！
As a bonus voice, there's the "Sleeping Polka" co-sleeping voice, or rather... Lewd lewd lewd lewd lewd!
いっしょに寝よっ。いっしょに寝よっ。寝ようね、みたいな、なんかそういったボイスになってます。
Let's sleep together. Let's sleep together. Like, "Let's sleep together," it's that kind of voice pack.
...もASMRになってます。
...is also an ASMR.
お〜！
Oh~!
よろしくお願いします！
Please check it out!
はい。
Yes.
恥ずかしいな、みんなとやるのこれ。
It's embarrassing, doing this with everyone.
なんか、エッチな女になってしまって...
I've become like some kind of sexy woman...
しー、しー、しー、しー。
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
恥ずかしい、すいません。
It's embarrassing, sorry.
いいじゃない。
It's fine!
すいません、新年も、えっと、皆さん改めて、これからよろしくお願いします。
Sorry. And once again, everyone, happy New Year, and please continue to support us.
お願いしまーす！
Please support us!
というわけでね、今日はみんなで最後一緒に歌を歌うために呼んできたということで、準備してきます！
And so, since I invited everyone here to sing the last song together today, we're going to get ready!
いってきまーす！
Here we go!
いってきまーす！ おっしゃー！ いくぞー！
Here we go! Let's do this! Let's go!
脚本は捨てちゃおっか
Let's throw away the script.
さあ、しかと焼き付けよ
Now, etch it firmly into your memory.
アドリブの熱いパフォーマンス
A hot ad-lib performance.
屋根裏を飛び出して
Jump out of the attic.
壮大なステージに響く
Resonating on a grand stage.
特別なストーリー
A special story.
瞼の裏には
Behind my eyelids...
虹が続く
A rainbow continues.
星空のメモリー
Memory of the starry sky.
等身大の愛を込めて
With all my love...
想像を超える世界へ
To a world beyond imagination.
誰も知らないでしょ
Nobody knows it yet, right?
Are You ready?
どんな未来が見に行こうよ
Let's go see what kind of future awaits.
なんて自由だ、笑っちゃうよね
How free it is, it's almost laughable, right?
ほら、ホログラムよりも先へ
Look, even further than the hologram.
誰だって置いていかないよ
We won't leave anyone behind.
ほら、歓声が呼んでいる
Look, the cheers are calling us.
スナップがパッと照らす
The snapshot lights up in a flash.
人生のスポットライト
The spotlight of life.
薔薇色のプレミアムショー
A rose-colored premium show.
ここが特等席よ
This is the best seat.
ポロマンス日和
A Pol-romance day.
元気次第のエチュード
An étude depending on your energy.
まるで物語
Just like a story.
捕まえてよ
Catch me.
（待って、ほら、待って）
(Wait, look, wait)
予想のできない展開に
In an unpredictable development,
ステージは揺れる
The stage trembles.
特別なストーリー
A special story.
耳を澄ましたら
If you listen closely,
雨粒のハーモニー
The harmony of raindrops.
浮かぶ、ふわふわな空想
Floating, fluffy fantasies.
暴走、底なしの本能
Running wild, bottomless instinct.
すべて知りたいでしょ
You want to know everything, right?
Hey Guys! 叫べ
Hey guys! Shout out!
気分は最高
Feeling great!
（最高！）
(Great!)
Come on! もっと叫べ
Come on! Shout more!
気分は最高
Feeling great!
（最高！）
(Great!)
ポルカ、終わるか？
Polka, is it ending?
終わらない！
It's not ending!
It's Showtime!
繋いだ手、離さないでなんてね
Holding hands, don't let go... just kidding.
どうしたって重くなっちゃって困るわ
I'm in trouble because it's getting heavy no matter what.
いつの日かエピローグを一緒に綴ろう
Let's write an epilogue together someday.
きっと約束だよ
It's a promise.
Life Goes On!
どんな未来が見に行こうよ
Let's go see what kind of future awaits.
なんて自由だ、笑っちゃうよね
How free it is, it's almost laughable, right?
ほら、ホログラムよりも先へ
Look, even further than the hologram.
夢のような花舞台に
On this dream-like flower stage,
感情を馳せたら
If we let our emotions run wild...
スナップがパッと照らす
The snapshot lights up in a flash.
人生のスポットライト
The spotlight of life.
薔薇色のプレミアムショー
A rose-colored premium show.
どこまでだって、咲き誇りたい！
I want to bloom proudly, wherever it may be!
ここが特等席よ
This is the best seat.
あんたにゃ もったいない あたしゃ 本当 ナイスバディ
You don't deserve me, I really have a nice body
自分でも言いたいくらい ただじゃない じゃない じゃない
I want to say it myself, I'm not cheap, not at all
熱けりゃ 冷ませばいい 寂しけりゃ エブリバディ
If it's hot, cool it down; if you're lonely, everybody
誰にも分からない 恋愛って いつ火がつくのか
No one knows when the fire of love will start
ダイナマイト
Dynamite
恋はダイナマイト
Love is dynamite
どんなに 不景気だって 恋はインフレーション
No matter how bad the economy is, love is inflation
こんなに 優しくされちゃ みだら
Being treated this kindly is lewd
明るい 未来に 就職希望だわ
I want to get a job in a bright future
日本の未来は 世界がうらやむ
The world envies Japan's future
恋をしようじゃないか DANCE! DANCING ALL OF THE NIGHT
Let's fall in love, shall we? DANCE! DANCING ALL OF THE NIGHT
なんだか 物足りない どこに立って 愛してほしいわ
Something's missing, wherever I am, I want to be loved
自分で 伝えるの 恥ずかしい じゃない ない
Telling you myself is embarrassing, isn't it?
理想の 二人だわ 憧れよ エブリバディ
We're the ideal couple, it's an aspiration, everybody
誰も 気づいてない 恋愛って 夢の落とし穴
No one has noticed, love is a dream's pitfall
ミステリー
Mystery
恋はミステリー
Love is mystery
そんなの 不自然だって 恋のインサイダー
Even if it's unnatural, love's insider
それでも 重宝されちゃ ラヴ
Even so, being cherished is love
幸せ 来る日も キャンセル待ちなの
Happiness is on the cancellation waiting list every day
あんたの笑顔は 世界がうらやむ
The world envies your smile
夢があるじゃないか DANCE! DANCING ALL OF THE NIGHT
There's a dream, isn't there? DANCE! DANCING ALL OF THE NIGHT
LOVE LOVE LOVE マシーン
LOVE LOVE LOVE Machine
LOVE LOVE LOVE ステーション
LOVE LOVE LOVE Station
LOVE LOVE LOVE ファクトリー
LOVE LOVE LOVE Factory
LOVE LOVE LOVE IS WONDERFUL
日本の未来は 世界がうらやむ
The world envies Japan's future
恋をしようじゃないか DANCE! DANCING ALL OF THE NIGHT
Let's fall in love, shall we? DANCE! DANCING ALL OF THE NIGHT
モーニング娘。も あんたもあたしも
Morning Musume, and you, and me
みんなも社長さんも DANCE! DANCING ALL OF THE NIGHT
Everyone and the company president too, DANCE! DANCING ALL OF THE NIGHT
LOVEマシーン
LOVE Machine
今日は主役だ！！まだまだかがやく場所へつれていくぜ！！ I LOVE YOU♡ 2026.1.30
Today I'm the star!! I'll take you to even brighter places!! I LOVE YOU♡ 2026.1.30
新曲のお披露目あり！
New song reveal!
Glitter of Love
ポルカのライブ過去最多 ホロメンゲスト10名
Polka's live with the most guests ever: 10 Hololive members